<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Geopolitics on BlockWireNews - Aggregated CryptoCurrency News</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/geopolitics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Geopolitics on BlockWireNews - Aggregated CryptoCurrency News</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/geopolitics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Midweek Market Pulse: Crypto Vibes and Global Ripples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/06202025_midweek_crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/06202025_midweek_crypto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://source.unsplash.com/1200x600/?cryptocurrency,chart&#34; alt=&#34;Crypto Market Overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hey squad! It’s hump day, and the crypto seas are anything but calm—so I’ve brewed an extra cup of coffee, stretched out my conference call legs, and dove into the charts. Let’s unpack the action from the last few days:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-bitcoins-see-saw-ride&#34;&gt;1. Bitcoin’s See-Saw Ride&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin flirted with $108K early Tuesday before a surprise shipping alert in the Red Sea sent risk assets skidding back to $105K. By Wednesday morning, it had staged a gutsy comeback to $107.5K—proof that dip-buyers are out in full force. If BTC can close above $108K by Friday, we might just see a mini-summer rally.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to the Grind: Post-Vacation Crypto Rundown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025-06-17-new-week-back-from-vaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025-06-17-new-week-back-from-vaca/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey gang, fresh off vacation and diving straight into this week&amp;rsquo;s &lt;strong&gt;weekly crypto market analysis&lt;/strong&gt;, we’ve seen &lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin price volatility&lt;/strong&gt; spike amid renewed Middle East tensions. Ethereum behaved like a &lt;strong&gt;safe haven asset&lt;/strong&gt;, while &lt;strong&gt;XRP ETF regulatory updates&lt;/strong&gt; kept traders on edge. Meanwhile, Polkadot’s &lt;strong&gt;developer summit highlights&lt;/strong&gt; are shaping future network strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend, renewed Israel–Iran skirmishes sent Bitcoin tumbling about 0.7% to roughly $106,120 before it bounced back toward $107K. Ethereum wasn’t spared either, sliding nearly 2.6% as traders fled to oil and gold for a safe haven. Even XRP wobbled around $2.08 before steadier hands pushed it back to $2.12—ETF chatter from Trump Media filing with the SEC might be the next spark to watch.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Send-Off: Final Crypto Lowdown from the Beach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025-06-13-end-of-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025-06-13-end-of-vacation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey crew, as I wrap up this &lt;strong&gt;crypto market wrap&lt;/strong&gt; from Bald Head Island, we witnessed a classic &lt;strong&gt;risk-off trading session&lt;/strong&gt; driven by recent &lt;strong&gt;Israel-Iran airstrikes&lt;/strong&gt;, which sent &lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin price volatility&lt;/strong&gt; through the roof—BTC briefly dipped below $103K before rebounding to $105K as traditional &lt;strong&gt;safe haven assets&lt;/strong&gt; like oil and gold surged (&lt;a href=&#34;https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-sinks-below-103000-as-israel-iran-conflict-sparks-global-crypto-selloff/articleshow/121820959.cms?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;Economic Times&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/dollar-other-safe-havens-rise-israel-strikes-iran-2025-06-13/?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;Reuters&lt;/a&gt;). Ether and XRP rode the same wave, down 4% and 3.5% respectively at the low. On the regulatory front, EU’s &lt;strong&gt;MiCA licensing&lt;/strong&gt; for Gemini and Crypto.com in Malta paves the way for harmonized crypto rules across Europe (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/crypto-giants-set-eu-green-light-amid-growing-regulatory-rift-sources-say-2025-06-13/?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;Reuters&lt;/a&gt;), while US-China trade talks continue to inject uncertainty into broader crypto liquidity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
