<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on BlockWireNews - Aggregated CryptoCurrency News</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on BlockWireNews - Aggregated CryptoCurrency News</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Collision: Trump vs. Musk Sends Markets Reeling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025-06-05-crypto-collision-trump-musk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025-06-05-crypto-collision-trump-musk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, this &lt;strong&gt;Trump Musk crypto feud&lt;/strong&gt; has unleashed extreme &lt;strong&gt;crypto market volatility&lt;/strong&gt;, with &lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin price fluctuation&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Ethereum market impact&lt;/strong&gt; rippling through every exchange. We saw &lt;strong&gt;memecoin price movement&lt;/strong&gt; explode—$Trump and Dogecoin faced wild swings—while &lt;strong&gt;XRP crash analysis&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Dogecoin market reactions&lt;/strong&gt; proved that &lt;strong&gt;political influence crypto&lt;/strong&gt; can trigger unprecedented panic in mere hours. Here’s the lowdown:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump vs. Musk: When Billionaire Beef Meets Blockchain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;On June 5, Elon Musk went full keyboard warrior, ripping into Trump’s “One Big Beautiful Bill” (seriously, that’s the name) for gutting EV incentives. He even floated impeaching Trump and starting a new centrist party—bold moves for a guy who just left a White House advisory gig. Naturally, Trump retaliated by threatening to yank Musk’s federal contracts (you know, the ones fueling SpaceX and Tesla) and calling Musk “crazy.” Musk then dropped a bombshell, alleging Trump had ties to the Epstein files—again, via X—so you can imagine how civil this got.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
